<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<command name='addAction' version='1.1' game='ofp' format='1'><syntax><return><value type='NUMBER' order='0'>The ID of the action is returned. IDs are incrementing. The first given action to each unit has got the ID 0, the second the ID 1 etc. ID's are also passed to the called script and used to remove an action with removeAction</value></return><param type='OBJECT' name='object' optional='f' order='0'>unit, vehicle or static object</param><array unbounded='f' optional='f' order='1'><param type='STRING' name='title' optional='f' order='0'>The action name which is displayed in the action menu, may contain XML like syntax. Because of that &lt; and &gt; symbols will be interpreted as opening and closing XML tags. To avoid this use &amp;lt; for &lt; and &amp;gt; for &gt;. The title text can be changed with setUserActionText</param><param type='STRING' name='script' optional='f' order='1'>Either path to the script file, relative to the mission folder or string with code or the actual script code. If the string is a path to script file, the script file *must* have extension .SQS or .SQF. The script, whether it is a file or a code, will run in scheduled environment, i.e. it is ok to use sleep. Parameters array passed to the script upon activation in _this variable is: [target, caller, ID, arguments] target (_this select 0): Object - the object which the action is assigned to caller (_this select 1): Object - the unit that activated the action ID (_this select 2): Number - ID of the activated action (same as ID returned by addAction) arguments (_this select 3): Anything - arguments given to the script if you are using the extended syntax<alt-types><t type='CODE'/></alt-types></param><param type='ANYTHING' name='arguments' optional='t' order='2'>Arguments to pass to the script (will be _this select 3 inside the script). If Array is used as an argument for example, its 1st element reference would be _this select 3 select 0. Default value: nil</param><param type='NUMBER' name='priority' optional='t' order='3'>Priority value of the action. Actions will be arranged in descending order according to this value. Every game action has a preset priority value. Value can be negative or decimal fraction. Actions with same values will be arranged in order which they were made, newest at the bottom. The bigger the number the higher the action will be positioned on the menu. Typical range is 0 (low priority. Eg: 'Get out') to 6 (high priority. Eg: 'Auto-hover on'). Default value: 1.5</param><param type='BOOLEAN' name='showWindow' optional='t' order='4'>If set to true, players see "Titletext" at mid-lower screen, as they approach the object. Only the title text for the action with highest priority and 'showWindow true' will be shown. Setting it to false disables the feature. Default value: true</param><param type='BOOLEAN' name='hideOnUse' optional='t' order='5'>If set to true, it will hide the action menu after selecting that action. If set to false, it will leave the action menu open and visible after selecting that action, leaving the same action highlighted, for the purpose of allowing you to reselect that same action quickly, or to select another action. Default value: true</param><param type='STRING' name='shortcut' optional='t' order='6'>One of the key names defined in bin.pbo (e.g. "moveForward"). Adding available shortcut will bind corresponding keyboard key to this action. Shortcut availability can be tested with inputAction command. Default value: ""</param><param type='STRING' name='condition' optional='t' order='7'>script code that must return true for the action to be shown. Special variables passed to the script code are _target (object to which action is attached to) and _this (caller/executing person). Default value: "true" NOTE: condition is evaluated on each frame in non-scheduled environment. If action is added to some object and not to player, condition will only get evaluated IF player is closer than 15m to the object AND is looking at the object. If action is added to player, the condition is evaluated all the time.</param><param type='NUMBER' name='radius' optional='t' order='8'>3D distance in meters the unit activating the action must be within to activate it. -1 disables this radius. Default (and max) value: 15</param><param type='BOOLEAN' name='unconscious' optional='t' order='9'>if true will be shown to incapacitated player (see setUnconscious, lifeState). Default value: false</param></array></syntax></command>